♪ Ain't cutting my hair, ♪
♪ till the Good Lord comes ♪
♪ Ain't cuttin' my hair ♪
♪ till the Good Lord come... ♪
Let's go, Teller.
Roll it up.
♪ Arrive upon the mountain ♪
♪ just to see what we've done ♪
♪ Cuttin' my hair, cuttin' ♪
♪ till the Good Lord comes ♪
♪ I ain't open my eyes ♪
♪ till we all are free ♪
♪ I ain't open my eyes, ♪
♪ till we all are free... ♪
♪ Till the color of our skin, ♪
♪ it don't mean a damn thing ♪
♪ I ain't open my eyes, ♪
♪ open till we all are free ♪
♪ I ain't pickin' up a paper ♪
♪ till the wild wind blows... ♪
Coming.
♪ I ain't picking up a paper ♪
♪ till the wild wind blows... ♪
Hi.
♪ I ain't pickin' up a paper ♪
♪ till the wild wind blows ♪
♪ Say what we should say until ♪
♪ we know we should know it ♪
♪ Pickin' up a paper, pickin' ♪
♪ till the wild wind blows ♪
♪ 'Cause it's a coal... ♪
♪ It's a coal war, ah-ah... ♪
Such a big boy.
Let's go.
Here we go. Here we go.
Oh, I know.
Look what Mama sucked out for
you this morning.
Look what Mama sucked out
for you, yes.
♪ I ain't cuttin' my hair, ♪
♪ till the Good Lord comes ♪
♪ Arrive upon the mountain ♪
♪ just to see what we have done ♪
♪ I ain't cuttin' my hair, ♪
♪ cuttin' till ♪
♪ the Good Lord comes... ♪
Door opening!
Breakfast.
♪ If we cannot see ♪
♪ all we destroy, we're blind ♪
♪ It's not the hand that cuts ♪
♪ it's the heart we left behind ♪
♪ It's not the hand that cuts, ♪
♪ it's the hatred deep inside ♪
♪ It's not the hand... ♪
♪ Not the hand...! ♪
♪
Gate!
Hey!
SAMCRO!
Gate!
Whoo-hoo!
It's good to see you
on this side, brother.
Shit, good
to be here, man.
Big day for both of us, huh?
Wouldn't do it
without ya.
We missed you
lunatics.
I knew you'd vote in
when I was gone, you pussy.
Thank you, Stockton.
It's been a real pleasure.
Let's get the hell outta here!
♪ 'Cause it's a coal... ♪
♪ It's a coal war ♪
♪ ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ It's a coal... ♪
♪ coal... ♪
♪ Five dollars and a head ♪
♪ to keep, the dull black scissors ♪
♪ and some kerosene ♪
♪ You burnt a house, ♪
♪ but you came to bid him well ♪
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ What a thing to tell ♪
♪ Put poison in the well ♪
♪ Just to say ♪
♪ Just to say... ♪
♪ I ain't cuttin' my hair ♪
♪ till the Good Lord comes ♪
♪ I ain't cuttin' my hair till ♪
♪ the Good Lord comes ♪
♪ Arrive upon the mountain ♪
♪ just to see what we've done... ♪
You're an artist, Floyd.
♪ I ain't cuttin my hair... ♪
Have a good day, Sheriff.
Thanks.
Still have small town values.
Sheriff.
♪ It's a coal war, ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ It's a coal... ♪
♪ coal... ♪
♪ It's a coal war, ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ It's a coal... ♪
♪ coal... ♪
♪
♪ I ain't cuttin' my hair ♪
♪ till the Good Lord comes ♪
♪ Ain't cuttin' my hair ♪
♪ Arrive upon the mountain ♪
♪ just to see what we've done ♪
♪ I ain't cuttin' my hair,
♪ cuttin' till the Good Lord comes ♪
♪ Till the Good Lord comes. ♪
Well, now, if you're
the welcoming committee, I was
kinda hoping for flowers,
maybe a bundt cake.
I'm sorry. No cake.
What the hell is this, man?
Just a friendly heads up.
Charming is now under under the
jurisdiction of the San
Joaquin Sheriff Department.
I'm guessing that's you.
Lieutenant Roosevelt.
Charming-Morada substation
is my command.
Well, you got to show
everyone how big your
stick is, Teddy.
Can we go now?
The conditions of your
release state that no gang
colors or identifying clothing
may be worn in public.
We're not a gang, we're
a motorcycle club.
Well, the Federal
Government disagrees.
So the next time I see
any one of you
who got out today
wearing cuts, well,
they'll belong to me.
We clear?
Welcome home, gentlemen.
♪ Riding through this world ♪
♪ All alone ♪
♪ God takes your soul ♪
♪ You're on your own ♪
♪ The crow flies straight ♪
♪ A perfect line ♪
♪ On the devil's bed ♪
♪ Until you die ♪
♪ Gotta look this life ♪
♪ In the eye. ♪
Sync, correction ilse for:
www.addic7ed.com
♪ Now I'm giving you the proff ♪
♪ last time you calling me a liar ♪
♪ This time I'm giving you
the proof... ♪
Hey.
Hey, history's dead,
sweetheart.
It's gotta stay that way, huh?
You okay?
Yeah. Anxious.
Mmm. I'm proud of you.
Ain't easy making things
work when they're inside.
You done great.
I couldn't have
done it without you.
Wasn't just me.
Was the whole club.
Yeah, it's true.
I love you.
Me, too.
Daddy's home.
Hey, you're here!
Whoo, yeah!
Say hi to Daddy.
Yeah!
How you doing?
All right?
Oh, someone's happy.
Hi, baby.
Oh, I'm so
glad you're home.
I love you.
I love you, too, Mom.
She did good.
Yeah, I know.
She did great.
Hey.
I picked out the one you wanted.
Where's Wayne?
I don't know.
He said he'd be here.
Really good to have
you back, Clay.
Holy shit, Chucky.
You got digits.
You grow those?
- It was Gemma.
- Gemma?
Yeah, I bought
him fingers.
Those shitty little nubs were
freakin' me out.
Were you freaking
her out?
Were you freaking her out?
Freaking her out!
Chapel ten minutes.
Yeah?
Sherriff Roosevelt.
I'm Linc Potter.
Assistant U.S. Attorney.
I, uh...
I have a, uh, card here
somewhere.
Ah.
It's uh...
There you are.
It's nice to meet you.
Same here.
All right.
We're renting some
space here, up on
the third floor.
Yeah, I've seen you
guys coming and going.
So, what can I do for you?
Well, uh, I was
hoping maybe you could
stop by later.
Want to bounce a few
things off of you.
Okay.
Officially?
Yes.
I talked to Sheriff Moore.
You're clear to join us.
Okay.
Mayor Hale.
Lincoln Potter
I've heard a lot of great
things about you, sir.
You're the AUSA.
That's right.
Well, uh, Sheriff, I
will see you later.
It was so nice to meet you.
Likewise.
What's that about?
Oh, probably just protocol.
You know, those guys been
setting up shop upstairs, in the
last two months.
How'd it go this
morning?
Without incident.
Clay and his boys got
the message.
I hope you don't
think one roadblock
is gonna get these
scumbags in line.
They've been quiet because
most of them have been inside.
- I'm on top of it.
- Oh, I know.
That's why I brought
the sheriffs here.
We need your kind
of law enforcement.
And that's what you're
gonna get, Jacob.
I've dealt with gangs for
the last 15 years, so...
Neutralizing their power's just
not going to happen in a day.
Of course not.
You and I both know there
are a lot of important things to
accomplish here in Charming.
I'm just trying to keep everyone
focused on those goals.
Yeah, I understand.
I understand.
And I appreciate that.
You let me know if you
need anything.
Thank you.
Your combat pay,
gentlemen.
I knew that two years
of community college
would pay off.
Even at a small
percentage
the new guns are pretty sweet.
Mayans, Italians, Niners,
everybody loves 'em.
The small percentages are over.
Piney, Ope...
Chibs, Kozik.
You did an outstanding job
holding us together, making
this new business work.
You did all the hard
work, brother.
We just grunted out the
day to day.
Well, you got my
deepest appreciation.
Absolutely.
Yes. Yeah.
Thanks, Ope.
You too, Chibby.
So, you know anything
new with our mayor's little
McMansion utopia?
Rich yuppies are
fleeing Stockton.
The city's a war zone.
We're hearing that Hale's
got a shitload of presales, and
just needs a few more investors
before he starts
swinging hammers.
This, um, Oswald
Construction bid, what is that?
Is that some sort of consolation
prize from Hale?
And when Hale pushed
that 99 on-ramp through the
City Council, all that
timberland went eminent domain,
and Elliot, you know,
lost millions.
So Hale, he's letting him make
it up with lumber and labor.
Yeah, Charming's
pretty much embraced it, Clay.
I mean, it'll provide
construction jobs,
doubles the output
at the mill...
Short term.
Hale's building homes in this
town that no one in
this town can afford.
Anybody else see a
problem with that?
I mean, Jacob Hale's been laying
this track for more than
five years now.
City councils, zoning
committees,
getting rid of Charming P.D.
No.
We're not gonna let this happen.
The black and proud
Sheriff Roosevelt.
Who the hell is he?
We don't know much.
He's out of a gangland task
force from Oakland.
He's been working ten months.
He's let us know he's
here, but this is
the first time he's
whipped his dick out.
Yeah, he's been
pretty low-key.
Yeah, not anymore.
Yeah, I guess today
was about letting us know
it ain't gonna be
business as usual.
Yeah. We're gonna
have to dig pretty
deep into this guy.
You're not gonna get
this sheriff on your payroll.
This boy's a straight-up cop.
All right.
The meet is set with Putlova.
The Jellybean Lounge.
What is it with Russians
and strippers?
They ain't strippers.
You been to the Jellybean?
It's horse meat in a g-string.
I love the Jellybean, man.
Of course you do.
I love it, too.
And the freak circle
is complete.
Ope...
- Everything set?
- Yeah. The Wahewa's
are gonna let us use the
southwest reservation.
You exit off at 18 miler.
Be there at 6:00.
And I know how much money is in
those envelopes, so those
wedding gifts better
not be bullshit.
All right.
We all got our marching orders.
Hey.
It's a very big day.
So let's get it done.
Clay.
We got company outside.
Two sheriffs, watching us
down the block.
Roosevelt.
He's probably going to tail.
Well, if he does,
he can't follow all of us.
I want, uh, Jax and
Opie with me.
Need the rest to
help get us there.
- Squiggy.
- Yeah.
I want you to drive
the tow-truck behind us.
Is that 'cause you're
upset with me?
We're on
parole, genius.
Can only congregate
if we're working.
I mean, come on, man.
I should be with you.
I'll be all right.
Need most of us
to stay detached.
We get the fun stuff.
Promise?
They're splitting up.
What do we do?
We stay with Clay.
What the hell is this?
They're boxing us in.
Goddamn it.
Clear the road.
Hey!
- Chibs!
- Whoa!
Son of a bitch.
I'm gonna kill these
pale bitches.
Why the confidentiality?
Peace of mind.
That way, you say anything
about what you see, I strip your
badge and throw you in jail.
I have some trust issues.
Please.
Some of these faces may
be familiar to you.
Jesus.
In 1970, Dick
Nixon signed into law the
Organized Crime Control Act.
Section 901 of that law...
Racketeer Influence and
Corrupt Organization Act.
Welcome to the war room.
Agents Lane, Kessler-- FBI.
Vance, ICE.
Woodrow, Grad, ATF.
Have a seat, Sheriff, please.
So you really think
you're gonna be able to
use RICO against the Sons?
The MC's become a
major distributer
for a group of Real IRA members,
modestly self-titled
the Irish Kings.
Struck a deal when they
were in Belfast last year.
Sons killed Jimmy O'Phelan;
IRA boss turned rat.
In return, the Irish
opened up their arsenal,
gave SAMCRO access to a
whole new caliber of weapons.
Pun intended.
So how do the Russians fit in?
The Russians were
providing a safe house for
O'Phelan in exchange for guns.
But they got a better offer
from the Sons.
Then Clay double-crossed
Putlova, took out Phelan,
left the Russians with zip.
And that's why Jax
Teller got shived in Stockton--
Russians' retaliation.
And to make peace,
Clay made a distribution
deal with Putlova.
They got the lion's share of the
guns and profits while
the MC was inside.
And now that the Sons are out,
all of that will be changing.
Yes, and as to, uh...
how, we'll know how
soon enough.
You have someone on the inside.
FBI Agent Ronald Worski.
Been undercover with the
Russians for over a year now.
He's very close to becoming
Putlova's number two.
We've tracked the
distribution from Belfast
and Dungloe over to Canada and
down the West Coast to Mendocino.
AK-47s, KG-9s, FN-57s, AR-15s.
Jesus.
Once our agent is
inside the circle,
we'll be able to get tape on
Putlova buying and
selling illegal arms.
And in one broad stroke,
we will take down the ROC
and by association, the Real
IRA, and the Sons of Anarchy.
And of all this is going
in Sanwa.
It's the only reason why you
would want to bring me in.
Yeah, most likely, it
will happen in your backyard.
But that is not the only reason
we're talking.
I checked your file,
talked to your superiors.
You have years of street time
with the local gangs and
players in Northern Cali.
We don't.
You're not here by default, sir.
You're here because
you can be trusted...
And because we need you.
Count me in.
Let's get him up to speed.
Welcome, gentlemen.
I trust you are healing well?
Fine.
Just business, right?
Yes.
I'm glad we could
settle all that.
It's not all settled.
You've been, uh, taking 80%
of the Irish stock for your
customers up north.
And 80% of
the risk as well.
We handled all the
transport and storage.
Well, now it's time for that
equal share scenario to kick in.
Yes, as we discussed,
you'll get 50% of the hardware.
But if we continue to transport
and house the guns, we
need to be compensated.
It's gonna take us a
little while to set up shop.
We'll give you five percent.
That's an awful lot of risk
and manpower for
just five percent.
Hey, we know how much you're
making running these guns.
Don't play broken
peasant with us.
Fair enough.
Five percent for
the first month
and 15%, if you stay longer.
Deal.
Uh, we're gonna want to see the
new merch. Get familiar with it.
I wanted to
bring it here.
We got some local
eyes on us.
We're hoping we could
see 'em tonight.
Check out your operation.
I thought tonight
was a celebration.
Yeah, we thought it'd be
good cover to get away.
Mm. Of course.
I'll make sure my men are there.
Great.
So we'll see you at the party?
I wouldn't miss
it for the world.
Well, here's to a long
and profitable relationship.
Na Zdorovie.
Jesus Christ!
I heard you!
You're gonna take it off
the goddamn hinges!
Sorry. I thought you
might have
upped and died on me in there.
Well, if I did, knocking
louder ain't gonna help.
Jesus, Wayne.
You told me you were gonna
hire somebody to help you out.
I don't need nobody
nosing around my shit.
Besides...
if you'd have called...
I might have had a chance
to clean up a little bit.
Your phone's been disconnected.
Oh.
Sit.
- What?
- Sit down.
Clay came home today.
You were supposed to come by.
Jesus Christ.
Was that today?
God...
I'm sorry, I... I just, uh..
I kinda lost track of time.
How are the new meds?
I don't know.
I quit taking 'em.
Wayne...
I can't afford 'em.
Coverage is shit.
I mean, all they do is make me
puke and sleep.
What's going on with you?
Just, uh...
living the dream.
Does, uh, Clay know about me
and Della splitting up?
Yeah.
I don't think he's privy to
your new rock star
lifestyle, however.
Right.
Noticed your plants
weren't doing so well out there.
Yeah...
Everything is just...
kinda dying on me.
Oh, shit.
I know, sweetheart.
Shit.
I know.
Dispatch, this is
SJ-19 for substation Morada.
Bobby, getting anything for Ope?
I was gonna give him cash.
How much you giving 'em?
A lot more than you,
you cheap-ass bastard.
I'm not cheap, just
mindful of excessive spending.
Dude, you re-use comdoms.
How about you, Juicy?
Giving them both ten
sessions at Clear Passages.
What?
It's he herbal colonic
and weed shop on Crestview.
I own 20%.
That is so disturbing.
Have you ever seen the
contents of a lower colon?
Oh, geez...
Stop!
And you tried to take 'em out?!
They boxed
us in, Luteniant.
I clipped one of 'em trying
to stay with Morrow.
Were they driving
the speed limit?
Maybe, at first,
but then they took off.
Must've been doing 110
on 18. It was crazy.
No shit.
These guys are smart.
They'll claim that you tried to
kill 'em, that they were
fleeing out of fear.
Then they'll try to sue us
for assault!
Just cut 'em loose.
And the next time you try to
play GTA on my watch,
I'm gonna bounce you
back to park duty!
Yes, sir.
Just heard from Worski.
Sons are meeting at the
warehouse tonight,
checking out the
Russian operation.
MC's not wasting any time.
Should I put a team
nearby, wire it up?
No, let's not risk it.
Sounds like it's just
a show and tell.
Let them all get friendly.
One big happy family.
The boys are napping.
Jax, stop!
I missed you so much.
Love me.
Damn, that was fast.
Yeah, that's 'cause
you're used to
speed-banging Juice
in dark hallways.
Hey, don't turn what
Juice and I had into
into something cheap and tawdry!
I'm sure it was sweet
Puerto Rican magic.
No more time, baby.
I don't think I can handle it.
Yeah, I know.
We're gonna be
all right, darling.
The Russians?
Handled.
These new guns gonna be our
golden ticket, Gem.
My finder's fee, my
new percentage...
I should bank around seven
figures before I'm done.
We are gonna be okay, baby.
No more killing ourselves.
I promise.
How bad are they?
The meds they gave me
inside didn't do very much.
I mean, it's all right on a day
like this when it's warm but...
I don't know how many
winters I got left.
One, two at the most.
There's plenty we can do.
I have Tara looking
into a good surgeon.
No, I ain't lettin'
nobody cut me open.
I'd have to step down to recoup.
Don't make any sense.
Well, we'll just,
we'll get better meds,
keep doing the cortisone.
You got plenty of time, baby.
Yeah.
I went to see Unser.
You gotta go out there, Clay.
He needs you.
He needs this club.
What he did for us...
Stahl.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
I think we should talk
about some things, Jax.
Yeah, we should talk
about all the chick shit
you decked out my house in.
I'm sorry, Maxim posters and
Harley mirrors aren't
really my style.
I want to talk about
the boys, Jax.
About what we're gonna do.
Sounds like someone else
wants a shot at those puppies.
Oh!
I'll get him.
Hey, you're supposed
to be gone by now.
It's bad luck to see the bride.
Just getting my stuff.
Figured I'd wear my
clean socks on the big day.
Wow, I'm honored.
You sure you want to do this?
It's kinda late to
back out now.
It's never too late to run.
I'm not running.
I'm not going away.
Like it or not, I'm part
of this family.
I like it.
And I'm happy that we're
going to be adding to it.
Hey, hey...
Look.
What is this?
All right, huh?
Come on.
There you go.
Here's Mommy.
Hey, hi, sweetie.
Hey, baby.
Hi.
Want to lie down?
Here you go.
Oh, my God!
It's beautiful.
Are you...?
Yeah.
We should get married.
Really?
I mean, you want... that?
I love you, Tara.
I've loved you since I was 16.
You stayed when anyone
else would've bailed.
You've given me a
beautiful son...
taken Abel on as your own.
I love you, too.
So much.
And I... I want all of that...
But...
I just...
I know this is who
you are, Jax and I...
I would never try to change
that-- the club, Charming.
I've learned so many things
while you were away.
So have I.
And I look at Thomas
and Abel, and I...
I think, how does this work?
How...
How do they grow up in this?
- Yes.
- I know.
And they're not going to.
What do you mean?
I realized you being with me
it's not some kind of accident.
It sounds crazy, but I think you were
put into my life to get me out, Tara
15 years ago.
And now.
I'm done with SAMCRO.
We both know, if I stay, I end
up back in prison or dead.
You say that now
because you just got out.
No. I've been coming
to this for a while.
The bond that holds this club
together isn't about love or
brotherhood anymore.
We lost that a long time ago.
It's just fear and greed now.
That's what your father
said in his manuscript.
Yeah.
He wanted to get out.
JT was a coward.
He lost himself in Irish pussy
and bailed on his family.
Instead of writing about it,
he should've done something.
He should've taken me and Thomas
and gotten the hell
out of Charming.
Hm, well, he would've had
to go through Gemma first.
Then he should've run
her ass over.
I'm not my father.
I'm not weak.
How do you get out?
Clay and Gemma will never let
you just leave.
We got a good thing
going with the Irish now.
It's smart, under the radar.
We'll be making big
money this year.
I just gotta hang out for a
while and earn.
How long?
More guns means more risk.
I don't have any skills, Tara.
I'm an okay mechanic with a GED.
The only thing I ever
did well was outlaw.
I just need to make some bank,
set myself up with something...
Jax, I can go anywhere.
I make good money.
I'm not gonna live off my wife.
I can't.
Look.
Clay's hands are going;
His days are numbered.
When he steps down,
he loses sway,
that's when I get out.
And Gemma...
she's just an old lady.
All this scares me.
I know. Hey.
You gotta trust me.
This is all I have
been thinking about
for the last 14 months.
I'm gonna finish up with SAMCRO,
then we're gonna take our boys
and we're gonna get
the hell out of here.
Start fresh somewhere.
Be a real family.
Hey.
What the hell you doing here?
Ah, I got a call.
Jed Clampett wants his
front yard back.
What?
It's my new style.
Retro redneck.
Good to see you.
Good to see you, too.
I'm, um... I'm sorry
I missed your homecoming.
Aw, that's all right.
I got some beer in the fridge.
I'm good.
I heard you sold the business.
Uh...
Controlling interest.
Still get a check every month.
Enough to keep me in the, uh,
lifestyle I'm accustomed to.
I see that.
Assume you're caught
up on the growth
and prosperity
of our little burg?
I saw it... riding in.
Also met Wild Black Hickok.
He, uh, provided me with the
interracial shadow.
Town's upside down, Wayne.
I know.
I'm not sure which
cancer's worse.
The one in me, or the
one in Charming.
Well...
You rotting away out here,
it ain't helpin' either one.
It don't hurt as much,
being unplugged.
Well, you're gonna have
to plug yourself back in, pal,
'cause... I need you.
I ain't gonna let Hale win.
There ain't gonna be no
Charming Heights.
How you gonna stop it?
Make nature take its course.
I got no idea what
the hell that means.
Other than it involves a lot of
shit and a big fan.
What do you need?
Still got access to
the rental trucks?
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna need one tonight.
Like, uh... catering trucks.
Something you might
see around a wedding.
What's it for?
You know.
Wedding shit.
He'll be asleep soon.
I got him.
Sweet dreams, douche bag.
How are the wrists?
A little sore.
How are yours?
Good.
♪ ♪
Congratulations.
They all here?
Yep.
It's a who's who of bad guys.
Niners, Mayans, Russians.
Love is in the air.
Keep your eye on that
party, make sure it doesn't
leave the reservation.
Brothers and sisters,
we come together today
under the all-seeing eye
of nature to witness the blessed
joining of Opie and Lyla.
I'd like to share with you
a blessing of the Apache.
Now you will
feel no rain, for each of you
will be shelter for the other.
Now you will feel no cold, for
you will always be warmth for
each other.
Now you will feel no loneliness,
for you will always be each
other's companion.
Now you are two persons, with
only one life before you.
May beauty and peace surround
you both in your journey ahead
and through all the years to
come.
You got
the... got the rings?
What?
With this ring, I vow
my love.
I promise to always be a
faithful and loving wife...
and old lady.
With this ring, I vow
my love.
And I promise always to cherish
and protect you.
What else?
And treat you as good
as my leather and...
Ride you as much as my Harley.
(all cheering, whooping,
applauding and laughing)
By the power
invested in me by the laws of
the Wahewa and the State of
California, I pronounce you
man and wife.
Have at it.
You get a hint of a
tale, you abort.
Yes, Mom.
Drink heavily for us.
Appreciate you giving
brown the nod inside.
Kept us alive while we figured
out our Russian problem.
Just protecting my interests.
Talked to our man yesterday.
All set up for tomorrow.
He should probably get
there first.
We got the local law
keeping tabs.
We should be safe
once we're inside.
I'll let him know.
Hey.
Let's dance.
Okay.
They call it the "Cop Killer".
It cuts through Kevlar and body
armor like soft cheese.
Very little kick.
The best wedding gift, ever.
Wait till you see Juice's gift.
You're gonna want to use
that on yourself.
New hand cannon.
Thank you.
And this next song is
a bride request.
Oh, I'm gonna want to
play with this.
It's your party.
Ope!
Come dance with me.
Yep.
Wow!
Barely an hour, and you're already
in the bowl covered in pussywhip.
Come on! It's our song.
Let's go check this shit out.
♪ I see trees of green
♪ Red roses, too
♪ I see 'em bloom
♪ For me and for you
And I think to myself... ♪
Spaceeba.
♪ What a wonderful world ♪
That's what I call a gun.
♪
♪ I see skies
♪ Of blue
♪ Clouds of white
♪ Bright blessed days
♪ Dark sacred nights
♪ And I think to myself
What a wonderful world... ♪
This is for Jax Teller.
♪ The colors of the rainbow
♪ So pretty in the sky
♪ Are also on the faces
♪ Of people going by... ♪
♪ I see friends shaking hands
♪ Saying, "How do you do?"
♪ They're really saying
"I... love... you..." ♪
Let's get these guns
in the truck.
♪ ♪
Just business.
♪ And I think to myself
♪ What a wonderful world
♪ The colors of the rainbow
♪ So pretty in the sky
♪ Are also on the faces
♪ Of people going by
♪ I see friends shaking hands
♪ Saying, "How do you do?"
♪ They're really saying
"I... love... you"... ♪
This is nice.
♪ I hear babies cry ♪
Yeah.
♪ I watch them grow ♪
It's good to be home.
♪ They'll learn much more
♪ Than I'll ever know
♪ And I think to myself
♪ What a wonderful world
What a wonderful world... ♪
Sync, correction by ilse for:
www.addic7ed.com